HIROTO ROBINSON

Web Developer

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Seattle USA

PHONE

252-269-9088

EMAIL

robinsonhiroto@gmail.com

SKILLS

React	
TypeScript	
JavaScript	
Git	
NextJS	
SQL	

HOBBIES

Chess, Video Games, Drawing, Watching Movies, Reading, General Learning

PROFILE

I'm a Full-Stack Web Developer with ~2 years of experience in Web Stacks involving Javascript/Typescript/React/NodeJS. Experienced in AGILE team environments collaborating to deliver custom ecommerce platforms to automate online business management and transactions. Quick thinking, communicative, and always learning, I strive to improve myself each day and hold accountability for the code I push.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Jr. Front End Developer, Clarity Ventures

Remote

Feb 2022 — Jan 2023

- Worked in AGILE team environments to design and develop 12+ custom e-commerce platforms, providing automated solutions to businesses expanding/revamping their online presence
- Developed architecture of 4 HIPAA-compliant solutions for clients, preserving data security alongside elegant storefronts.
- Maintained client interactions spanning discovery meetings and working sessions for first hand knowledge of client's needs
- · Assisted heavily in code base transition from AngularJS to React
- Utilized Azure for manual/pipeline deployments of client sites and for task management via Azure's kanban

Freelance, Self-Employed

Seattle

Jun 2021 — Jan 2022

- Architected, developed, and maintained websites for various small businesses using Typescript/Gatsby
- Handled IT issues for sites, maintaining mail server and content updates
- · Marketed services to the Greater Seattle Area
- Managed/maintained client satisfaction and provided insight on direction of online business presence

LINKS

<u>linkedin</u>

Github

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development, University of Washington Bootcamps

Seattle

Mar 2021 — Jun 2021

- · Grade: A+ Average
- 12 Week Intensive Course covering web development languages such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript(ES6+), Handlebars, and SQL.
- Libraries included React, Node, Express, mySQL, Sequelize, Mongoose, MongoDB, and more.
- Gained in depth and hands on knowledge and practice with OOP, data structures, algorithms, RESTful practices, Agile methodologies, as well as MVC * CORS architecture.

REFERENCES

Jesse Webb

Clarity Ventures

jesse.webb2@gmail.com 385-236-6936

Tristan Moon-Keca

Clarity Ventures

tmoonkeca@gmail.com 780-722-9753

Patrick Wang

BrainGu

(512) 554-6614